Come my love, Moi Moi
Kune, a fortuitous moment.
My heart goes thump for you.
Japan's first ever maid, Omoi.
In early Meiji, when social stratification
was still ingrained in society?
She served all masters
without distinction.
and enamored the people of Akiyo
Nahara with love and violence.
After her death,
an annual festival called the Lady Omoi
Climb was established in her honor.
It is a fighting festival
where maids compete
to be the best of the
best in the name of honor,
pride, and respect.
You're welcome!
It's delicious!
It's the best
for you
guys!
We are blessed!
She should be the one who wants
to keep it She's so happy!
She's so happy!
What are you doing!?
I'm glad you are so happy!
I'm made way!
I'm full of the fan here to do do do!
That's all!
Shake your hand!
Made of princess!
So, I hear you've been
raking it in recently.
Well, I guess I can't complain.
You know, there's some
shady rumors out there.
I hear your cafe's bringing
in clients by dealing drugs.
What?
Of course, Little Teddy here
doesn't believe any of that.
But if Miss Nagi were to catch
wind of such a rumor you know
what killed the bear I'll have
you stuffed bring it on cat girl.
I'll skin that pretty hide of yours
and make some slippers out of it
Sit down yes ma 'am
This year's Akiba maid festival
will be special in that the
creature land group will be the
sole organizer That's great news,
now that those pesky ETs are gone.
Having a single group organize the
festival is a first in Akiba history.
That's right.
For the Lady Omoe climb, we will
be overseeing the arrangements.
So therefore, all the cafes
must know that Dazzlion,
Miss Nagi's cafe, is supposed to win.
The time has come.
We will show Akiba that we are the
ultimate ecosystem of creatures.
Wow! Awesome! What is that?
That's Lady Omoe.
We all get to climb her at
the end of the festival.
That sounds really fun!
You think maids kicking and
fighting each other is fun?
They fight?
The maid who reaches the top first
becomes Lady Omoe for the year.
That means better priority in the
group and more customers for her cafe.
What?
Then we should totally go for that!
No way, dude!
The starting order for the Lady
Omoe climb is based on food sales.
Last year, the race was over before
we even got to the starting line.
But if we work really hard
on the food stall, then we...
Ugh, I thought I smelt
swine flesh. No wonder.
Uh, can I help you?
Uh, what are you trying to say, swine?
Why are you even talking?
You greedy hogs have been
rather a piggy recently.
Or is it uppity?
I wouldn't say that if I were you.
A couple of newbies put some silly ideas
into those swollen heads of yours, huh?
That's not true.
Of course it's not.
You know you pigs are always
at the bottom of the heap.
Stupid.
You can have at it with
non-affiliates all you want.
Just make sure you comply to
the creature pecking order.
Sweet panda.
Oh, kachimachi! Water! We need water!
How could they be so awful?
It's just what we get as
a cafe ranked dead last.
We hardly run into maids from other
affiliated cafes outside the festival,
so they love getting the chance
to make fun of us every year.
It's not like you two to
put up with trash talk.
There's no point in going
against a higher ranked cafe.
What she said.
You don't want another bloody
turf war on our hands, right?
Well, no, I guess not, but...
Come on, let's get this tent up
and go help Bronco and the others.
These are the guidelines
for this year's festival.
Read it over thoroughly. Okay, creature.
Remember, this year's
festival is a special one.
Read every single word carefully.
And make sure to beat them into
the heads of your pigsty maids.
Okay, creature.
Huh?
Good evening, sir.
You better make sure your
tiny pig brains understand.
I wonder what that was about.
Ugh, so teeny-weeny. Chief?
Hey, welcome back.
Pig's feet?
Yeah, we sold colored piglets last year.
Colored piglets?
But why sell those?
There are plenty of other festival
stalls like shaved ice and candy apples.
The higher-ranked cafes
take all the good ones.
We're too bottom-rung to
get to do anything cool.
Bottom-rung?
Well, you know, they say pig's feet
are a great source of collagen.
What does she mean by bottom rung? Oh.
Our group has what they
call the moi-moi hierarchy,
and our cafe is ranked at the very bottom.
Why are we ranked so low?
Well, see?
Cafes that do dirty work for the
higher-ups, or offer lots of honey money,
or have a bond of sisterhood with
a better cafe are ranked high.
We have none of that, so
we're down at the bottom.
Get it?
Yes, I understand the structure. Bottom?
Can we cut this talk?
It's a real total buzzkill.
You're right.
We just have to stick it out for the
festival and just keep our heads down
Zoya, can you break down
and bundle the empty boxes?
Sure.
There we go.
What is the meaning of this?
Are you worried that
we might actually lose?
Oh, of course not.
We just devised a brilliant
plan to ensure total
line victory What is Miss
Nagi worried about then?
We are the king of beasts
after all We don't need
your stupid plan to win
the Lady Omaway Climb.
But of course not.
Your victory will surely be indisputable.
This is but a formality.
Go tell Miss Nagi that we lions will
show her an elegant victory indeed.
Maureen! Maureen!
You roar!
What an honor, ma 'am!
Oink-y-doink. It's me.
Yes, Master Creature!
I'm running a final check about
the guidelines I gave you.
I trust your maids all know the deal.
Oh of course they do.
If you pigs were to violate
the terms in the guidelines,
we will disown you along
with all the other dogs.
Is there a problem?
No, not at all.
Crap. Crap. Crap.
The guidelines.
Oh, there's somewhere around here.
I swear it was here, wasn't it?
Huh? What the?
Looks flashier than yesterday,
huh? Oh! Good morning!
Nagomi?
It's a festival, after all!
It's a shame to have
to keep our heads down!
If we make lots of masters happy, I'm
sure it will be that much more fun!
You've been at this since the morning?
Yep!
Your face is smudged.
Wipe it off later.
Well, we might as well
enjoy the festival, dudes!
So cuter, so better, I say! Exactly!
Let's do our best!
Ronco is something wrong I hope not have
you guys seen the chief anywhere huh?
Whatever it doesn't make a difference
either way come on let's sell some
Pig's feet man I feel bad about this
they're probably all panicking right
now With me missing oh fishy now
welcome home welcome home all masters and
We truly appreciate seeing such a
large turnout for today's festivities.
Every single maid cafe in
Akiba is gathered here today.
We cover every genre of moe.
So today, the sky's the limit for moe.
A moe moe festival.
Moe till you drop.
The Akiba Maid Festival begins now.
Pig's feet?
Yes!
Would you like one?
Sorry, uh, I need to go to the bathroom.
The port-a-potties are
all that way, Master.
Thank you.
We're not here to point out
the port-a-potties, geez.
It's been how many times now?
That was the 26th time.
Greetings, Master.
Allow me to welcome you.
Ms.
Runko, I just love pig's feet.
Would you wrap up two pigs worth for me?
Gladly, Master. Please wait here.
That customer's totally
after Ronco, isn't he?
He's been at the cafe a lot recently.
Yeah, I think he's super cute.
I'll stop by the cafe again.
We eagerly await your
return to the pigsty.
What did he put into your bowl, Ronco?
Acorns.
That's what pigs love best.
So this is a pig's foot?
Very interesting.
Detectives are first for me.
Oh, masters! I'm glad you came!
We searched all over the venue for your
stall, but we couldn't find you on the map.
We almost gave up.
Master, may I take a look at that, please?
Oh, sure. Of course.
Huh?
Think this might be us?
Does it all stand for Port-O-Potties?
That's why they keep asking
us where the bathroom is.
So they really don't give
a crap about us, huh?
No wonder no one's coming to see us.
If they're not going to come to
us, we'll just go out to them.
Come get some pig feet from Oinky Doink!
Freshly chopped off, ripe pig feet!
They're hogalicious!
Get your pig feet!
Fresh pig feet from Oinky Doink!
My fresh pig's feet!
Nogomi!
Where's your porking manager?
You really suck at life, you know that?
You can't do anything right.
Nothing good has ever happened
to you your entire life.
You really think so? Sure do.
They'll figure things out.
They're smart girls.
They don't need you
around fucking it all up.
Maybe you're right.
I mean, no one's out
looking for you right now.
So go ahead and just make a run for it.
That's not a bad idea.
Maybe I will after I catch a fish.
Hey, bozos.
Where's your manager? Tell us now.
She's not here.
Is there something we can help you with?
This pig head was walking around
snorting and selling stuff.
You're gonna have to pay.
How about we ram those pig's feet in
your ears and rattle your molars around?
Huh?
Zoya, what's wrong?
You got a problem?
Sounds like you're wanting a beating, huh?
Now's not the time.
We're very sorry.
This scared little piggy here is smart.
She knows her place in the ecosystem.
Yumechi.
Hands on the ground, all of you.
Come on now, hurry it up.
All right, I'll do it.
Don't, Yumechi!
I went out there all of my own! I'm sorry!
I'm so very sorry!
You think your groveling
actually means anything, idiot?
Huh? Ow!
Come on, hurry the hell up. Of course.
Yumechi, don't do it! It's fine.
We're so very sorry.
Here's a hoofprint for you.
This way you won't forget
your place, you hear me?
Don't you dare leave your pigs die again.
Pigs are supposed to keep their noses
to the ground and stay rooting around.
That way, maybe you'll find a
truffle or something once in a while.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gone out there.
I should have stayed put.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
If we fight back, they'll
close us down this time.
We have to let it go.
No, that's not what I'm getting at.
I don't get why Oinky Doink
is on the bottom rung?
As I see it, you're all top-notch maids!
You think we're top-notch?
Ronko's right, you guys?
Yumechi has given up
being human in a good way.
Shippon is crazy hyper and ready to party!
And Zoya is so much better at smiling now.
Ronko's ketchup doodles
aren't awful anymore.
They're better than mine.
And Okachimachi is a real panda.
You're all really amazing maids!
Then, let us prove it.
How do we do that, Zoh?
That's an easy answer.
Just what do you think
our pig's feet are for?
Moimoy QQN! Moimoy QQN!
Moimoy QQN!
Moimoy QQN maybe!
Apparently, we have the highest
attendance in the history of the festival.
Great.
Let's go over the plan.
Maids who contribute to the group
will gain wealth, fame, and power.
Maids who fail will get cast to
the bottom to serve as a lesson.
Do I make myself clear? Yes.
We've made sure to ingrain
the Moe-Moe hierarchy.
It will definitely benefit the group.
So now the Creatureland
group's ecosystem is undivided.
It's not just the Creatureland group.
Akiba itself is a creature that thrives
off of people's innate yearning for greed.
So, today I'll prove that
I'm at the apex of Akiba.
King of beasts!
King of Akiba!
All right, huffers, got the
guidelines in your head?
We make things look extremely
close and make sure the lions win.
Remember, we're goners if we take
even a single step out of line.
Come on, Moo Moo!
You've got to win it this year!
That's right!
We're going for the win!
Moo! Moo!
Let's win round! Bear!
You all ready?
Yes!
Let's win this!
Yes, that's me!
We'll show them, this year's different!
Let's show them what pigs
are made of! Okie dokie!
Okie doink!
Masters and mistresses,
please cheer them on until the bones in
your throat get pulverized into dust.
Once they start running, they can't stop.
Anything goes from Moe Moe to Bashity
Bash, a festival melee, the main event.
The Lady of Moe Climb is about to begin.
Moe, Moe, baby.
Go, get away.
Aren't we allowed to go yet, Rocco?
They sounded the gun a little while ago.
There's no reason we should
have to wait quietly.
Let's go then!
Easy spin, pig mix.
Wait, what are you doing?
Didn't you retry the
ecosystem into your head?
Here comes Doinky Doink! Yeah!
Big go-go!
Don't think I know that, Kefé. Those pigs?
What is going on out there?
Those fucking pigs.
Comply with the ecosystem!
Let us through!
Stick to the guidelines.
Fucking swine!
Whoa, are you kidding me?
Are the underdogs trying
to win this thing?
Don't worry!
This doesn't change the fact
that the lions will win!
Huh?
What the hell is going on?
We're almost at the top!
You think it's okay for
you damn pigs to be here?
Whatever, like we give a care!
Haven't you read the damn thing?
Like hell we're gonna read the room!
No, that's not what I mean!
Just shut the hell up!
Yimachi! On it!
Even a pig.
We'll climb a tree if
you flatter them enough!
That'll make you quit that silly snorting.
Good work, lions.
Damn it.
That's it, then.
Here it comes, here it comes!
My first catch of the day!
Nogome?
Are you going to die?
You little...
I'll go and do it!
Whoa!
Nogome!
Stop now!
This is for your own good!
That's far enough!
Please listen!
Be a good pig and back down!
I'll give you a salmon!
Take that!
Stupid pig!
This is full already!
You hogs should stick to selling
pig speed by the port-a-potties!
I got the pig's foot you ordered
right here, mistress. Runco!
We are done here!
Runco!
Nogomi, allow me to send you off.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Oh no, our ecosystem's done for.
This is the end.
Hmm.
Looking for a real hectic time?
Come to Oink and Doink,
Captain! Yeah! Do it!
Do it!
Fucking pigs At the top of the ecosystem
Thank you very much the time has
now come we will award the winner
of the lady omoe climb Our new
lady omoe maid will stand at the
very pinnacle of all akiba maids
for the coming year She will
provide her very special service to
all of you masters and mistresses.
Here now, to present the
officious lady on my own title,
is the head representative
of the Creatureland Group,
Miss Nagi!
Head representative?
She's gone and done it now.
Yeah, she said for sure.
What a surprising result.
You have plenty of promise, Pig.
Thank you very much, Madam Creature.
Congratulations, Oinky-Doy! Oh, cool.
We should go check them out.
Whether this newfound maid standing here
is truly worthy of being Our Lady Omoe?
is a question we will all soon find out.
Speak.
Right!
I'm Nagomi from Oinky-Doy Cafe.
Masters, mistresses, we eagerly
await your return to our pigsty!
Hey, look!
That's one of our maids!
The one who's making the speech now!
I practically raised her.
It's the end of my heart,
but it's the end of my heart,
but it's the end of my heart.
Take a moment, tell us to be